mobstudio.ru 2019-12-02

# Galaxy Privacy Policy

What personal information do we collect?

We collect personal information from you when you register on Galaxy.

When registering on Galaxy, you are asked to enter your email address. You may, however, register on Galaxy without entering this personal information.

What do we use your personal information for?

The personal information we collect from you may be used to recover your account if you lose your recovery code. Your personal information helps our Support Service Team to faster provide you with a recovery code to your account.

We do not send periodic emails and don’t use your email address to administer contests, promotions, surveys or other similar material.

How do we protect your personal information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information.

Third party links

Galaxy includes or offers third party sites that are considered to be partner sites. Occasionally any other third party sites may be offered by Galaxy users. Nonetheless we moderate Galaxy content and try to eliminate any third party links except ones that lead to our partner sites. 

We have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of any third party sites including our partner sites.

License Agreement

Please also visit our License Agreement establishing restrictions and responsibilities governing the use of Galaxy http://in-galaxy.com/pages/license/

Your Consent

By using Galaxy, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

Changes to Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This Privacy Policy was last modified on August 14, 2012.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us using the email below:

mobstudio@mobstudio.ru
